universumglobal.com 2009-06-18

# 

At Universum, we understand that privacy is an important issue for users of (visitors to) the Universum Internet site www.universum.com and its related domains. The following information is designed to help visitors understand what information we collect from our site, and how we handle and use the information after that.

### Information collection and use

Ericsson is the sole owner of any information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Ericsson may collect information from our users at several different points on our website. Ericsson may also transfer the information collected to any relevant unit within Ericsson, and located anywhere in the world.gdfgdfgd

### General enquiries

If a user contacts Ericsson with a general enquiry, the user may need to provide Ericsson with personal information (for example contact details). Ericsson will use this personal information to respond to the enquiry and track further correspondence. Information is also used to compile statistics on response handling, etc. This is done in aggregate, and no individual names or other personal information are retained. Personal information collected is not used for any other purpose.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that a site transfers to a user's (visitor's) hard disk or browser for added functionality or for tracking site usage. In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, Ericsson may use cookies to determine the path users take on our site and to identify repeat users of our site. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person's name or e-mail address.

Cookies can be saved to the hard disk, but so-called session cookies are saved to the browser only and disappear when the browser is closed. On the ericsson.com homepage (and similar top or index pages), we use cookies that are saved to the hard disk and therefore remain after the browser is closed. Such cookies determine the path users take on our site and also identify repeat users of our site, although not by names or email addresses. On other pages of our site, we use session cookies to determine the path users take on our site. On some pages, we may also use non-session cookies.

It is possible to configure your browser to reject cookies by modifying the browser settings or preferences. If you wish to do so, we recommend you consult the information provided in the browser or contact the browser vendor for help and instructions.

Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis.
